Today, Aaliyah has invited Noah to a meeting to introduce herself as Chief Transformation Officer.
Aaliyah wants to discuss how she, Noah and the Digital department are going to collaborate
to ensure a successful transformation.
What’s next on the agenda?
My meeting with Aaliyah.
What’s this about again?
Right — the transformation.
Ugh.
Last time we had a transformation, my team wasn’t happy.
She already has some hard deadlines in mind.
Ahh! I am so hungry!
Why on earth do people schedule meetings at lunchtime?
Okay, I have a meeting with Noah soon.
I can’t wait to have some extra brain power on this.
Oh, everything’s starting to catch up with me these days.
My personal training, the women’s mentorship initiative, my local youth group — and now this
transformation.
Aaliyah, stop!
Breathe.
Remember what your meditation app tells you to do.
Breathe in the positive energy.
Breathe out the negative energy.
I’m confident my team can make this work.
Aaliyah! How are you?
Oh, hey! Oops — let me get these crumbs off my desk.
I’m so sorry, I promise I don’t usually have meetings over lunch.
No worries.
Oof, it’s been one of those days, Noah.
Thank you for being flexible.
You know, I realised I’ve been here five years and I’ve never had the chance to work with you.
I know! Kind of hard to believe.
I bet we’ll make a great team.
Absolutely. So I wanted to take some time before our full team kick-off to get to know each other a little better.
We’ll be working closely together, so I really want us to have a clear sense of our roles in the transformation.
Anything else that you think would be helpful for us to talk about today?
Well, it would be helpful if you just share your plan and deadlines so my team can keep up with you.
Then I’ll know whether we can deliver.
You can’t say that.
Aaliyah looks like she’s in a tight spot right now with everything that’s been going on.
Starting off on the right track means putting yourself in the other person’s shoes.
What are they thinking and feeling? And why?
What is at stake for them?
Taking the time before and during your conversation to recognise where someone is coming from
can help you meet them where they stand.
To be honest, Aaliyah, it would be great to start off by learning more about you.
How are you feeling in the new role?
I bet you’ve got a lot on your plate right now.
I know — I didn’t expect the transformation to kick off this early,
so I’m trying to wrap up a bunch of different things on my to-do list.
Aaliyah,
you’re not alone.
You have a great team here to support you.
But you know what?
Let’s go introduce you to the rest of the team.